Archit Kheni

iOS Developer & Flutter Developer with 3 years of Experience No. 74058 14315 Email: kheniarchit8900@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Proactive Flutter Developer with 3 years of experience delivering enjoyable mobile products per the client's requirement. Developed and marketing materials for 15 apps at Einfach Infotech, 2 of which were featured in the App Store skilled with Swift, UIKit, Flutter, Dart, Firebase, and API Integration.

SKILLS

I Have expertise in Swift, UIKit, Flutter, Dart, firebase, APIs Integration, Fire store, And Widget Integration

EXPERIENCE

Currently working (Einfach Infotech) — Sr. Flutter Developer

February 2021 - PRESENT

• As a Senior Flutter Developer, I completed many projects as per the client's requirements. Also, I played the role of team leader.

Fluense Solutions, Surat — Flutter Developer

November 2019 - January 2021

• I took my training under an experienced Developer and start my Developing career & Promoted to TL In Short Time.

PROJECTS

Gym star: My Gym Buddy — Flutter Front-end Developer

https://apps.apple.com/in/app/gymstar-my-gym-buddy/id1234015763

Flutter, Dart

02 Month

Map buzz: — iOS Development

https://apps.apple.com/in/app/mapbuzz/id956545196

Flutter, Dart, API Integration, Map Integrate

04 Month

DRAGON LTC SOLUTIONS: — Flutter Developer

https://apps.apple.com/in/app/dragon-ltc-solutions/id1531698405

Flutter, Dart, API Integration, Chat Function, Agora Integration 03 Month

EDUCATION

P.P. Savani University, Surat — Computer Science

Jun 2017 - March 2019, Surat

AWARDS

- · I received Employee of the Month
- · Mentorship or leadership awards

.